Even though we are living in an age where growing old is thought of as an inevitable misery, this doctor has been changing the game for seniors over the last 25 years.
尽管在我们所处的这个时代，人们把变老看作一种不可避免的痛苦，但过去25年来，这位医生一直在为老年人改变游戏规则。
It all started in 1991 when the Harvard-educated physician was transferred from working in a stressful emergency room to being the medical director of a nursing home in upstate New York.
这一切始于1991年，那一年，这位哈佛出身的医生从压力很大的急诊室调到纽约州北部的一家养老院，担任医疗主任。
The depressing and regimented environment got him thinking about what exactly could improve the residents’ conditions.
那里令人压抑、管制严格的环境让他开始思考：究竟什么能够改善入住老人的状况。
Even though animals in nursing homes were illegal at the time, Dr. Bill Thomas took a chance.
尽管当时在养老院里养动物是违法的，比尔·托马斯医生还是冒险一试。
Acting on a hunch, he brought in two dogs, four cats, hens, rabbits, 100 birds, a multitude of plants, a flower garden, and a vegetable patch.
他凭直觉行事，引进了两条狗、四只猫、一些母鸡和兔子、100只鸟以及大量植物，还开辟了一座花园和一块菜地。
The change was dramatic.
变化非常显著。
There was a 50% drop in medical prescriptions along with a dramatic decrease in death rates—but most importantly, the residents were simply happier.
医疗处方减少了50%，同时死亡率大幅下降，但最重要的是，入住老人就是比以前快乐了。
Dr. Thomas’s approach, named the Eden Alternative, has driven nursing homes to allow a more autonomous and creative living space for their elderly.
托马斯医生的方法名为“伊甸园替代模式”，它已促使养老院给予院内老人更自主、更有创造性的生活空间。
It erases the belief that growing old means growing useless.
它消除了这样一种观念：变老就意味着变得无用。
He encourages residents to think of their age as an enriching new phase of life rather than the end of it.
他鼓励入住老人把自己的年纪看作人生中一个丰富充实的新阶段，而不是人生的终点。
Thomas, now a speaker and author of several books, also created small, independently run residences with their own bedrooms and bathrooms, and he has been preaching a singular message that getting old is not a bad thing.
托马斯如今是一名演说家，也是好几本书的作者。他还创办了一些独立运营的小型住所，里面配有独立的卧室和浴室；他一直在宣扬的只有一个理念：变老并不是一件坏事。
“Within six weeks, they had to send a truck around to pick up all the wheelchairs,” Thomas told the Washington Post.
“六周之内，他们就不得不派一辆卡车过来，把所有轮椅都收走，”托马斯对《华盛顿邮报》说。
“You know why most people in nursing homes use wheelchairs?
“你知道养老院里的大多数人为什么坐轮椅吗？
Because the buildings are so big.”
因为那些楼太大了。”
The 56-year-old doctor’s methods have been adopted in Australia, Japan, Canada, and America with enormous success.
这位56岁医生的方法已在澳大利亚、日本、加拿大和美国得到采用，并取得了巨大成功。
Last year he published Second Wind: Navigating the Passage to a Slower, Deeper, and More Connected Life, a guide on how to shift our perspectives on aging and growth.
去年，他出版了《重振活力：顺利过渡到更从容、更深刻、联系更紧密的人生》，这本指南讲的是如何转变我们对衰老和成长的看法。
He is currently traveling through North America performing with his guitar and his enthusiasm on his Age of Disruption Tour.
他目前正在北美各地开展“颠覆时代”巡回演出，带着吉他、满怀热情地登台表演。